vidadivina.com 2019-07-14

# Vida Divina

                            Vida Divina® Privacy Policy
         OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY
         Our Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products
         and services with integrity in dealing with users. The Policy is designed to assist you in the understanding
         of how we collect, use and protect the personal information provided to us.
         THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
         When you visit our site, we collect two types of information: personal information you actively choose to
         disclose (“Active Information”) and information not visible to you that arises out of your browsing of our
         site (“Passive Information”). Please note that passive Information is collected on an aggregate and
         anonymous basis.
         Personally Identifiable Information
         Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies and is reasonably linked to you.
         Registration
         When you register to become an authorized reseller of our products or services, we will collect Personally
         Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number). This Personally
         Identifiable Information is securely stored and may be accessed on our website. You are assigned an
         identification number and select your own password – both are needed to enter the Site and to access
         your Contact Information. Please safeguard your password in a secure location as we are not responsible
         for breaches into the system when access is willingly provided.
         Ordering
         When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as
         name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transactional information). We use this
         information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate the status of your order.
         Credit and Debit Card Storage
         Credit and debit card information collected at registration or for product orders is used only to process
         payment for the transaction and, generally, is not retained on our Site. However, you may voluntarily elect
         to securely store multiple credit cards to be used for product orders.
         Surveys and Promotions
         Occasionally, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and
         questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products and
1700 S. Miliken Ave. | Ontario, CA. 91761 | www.vidadivina.com | p: +1(909) 333 5443 | e: compliance@vidadivina.com
                                     ©2019 Vida Divina® Worldwide. All Rights Reserved | Rev: 01-01-19

         services and to ensure that we’re providing accurate disclosures. We may also use your Personally
         Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information that coincide with your
         preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences, or let us know if you do not wish to receive
         any promotional materials, by adjusting your Subscriptions & Email options on the Site.
         Active Information You Choose to Provide
         In order to gain use of the site (become a “user”), we require you to disclose the following information:
         Name, Address and Phone Number
         We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you submit to
         us when you use our secure online forms. The information you provide to us is stored securely.
         Passive Information
         We store and collect various types of passive information on an aggregate and anonymous basis. This
         information may include such technical information as it pertains to your Internet protocol address, your
         device operating system and browser type, cookies, and an address of a referring website or any other
         path you take to reach our website all described in greater detail below.
         Aggregate Information
         This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information
         would include the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website that referred you to our Site, your
         Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf
         the web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our
         web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its
         effectiveness, and improve the content or our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable
         experience.
         We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate
         Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any
         Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do
         correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable
         Information under this Privacy Statement.
         What is a Cookie?
         Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to
         access a site. They are small pieces of data stored by a user’s browser to simplify subsequent
         interactions with the site. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete
         transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more
         personalized. Our site utilizes cookies to collect information about how our site is used. Passive
         Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site,
         the sites visited just before and just after visiting our site. If you do not wish to transmit “cookie”
         information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser.
1700 S. Miliken Ave. | Ontario, CA. 91761 | www.vidadivina.com | p: +1(909) 333 5443 | e: compliance@vidadivina.com
                                     ©2019 Vida Divina® Worldwide. All Rights Reserved | Rev: 01-01-19

         Our site’s servers also automatically identify your computer by its Internet Protocol address, which is a
         unique string of numbers that are assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. The IP
         address may be used to address problems with our server or to gather broad demographic information
         about our users. We passively collect your IP Address.
         HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
         Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, use Active
         Information for purposes of administering our core business functions, such as the fulfillment of orders or
         services, the furnishing of customer care and support, and supplying the availability of other products or
         services we think might be of interest to our users.
         We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance our site to make it
         easier, faster and friendlier for users. Additionally, cookies help us better understand the usage pattern of
         the people that visit our site, which helps us improve our services. Passive Information may result in your
         viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits.
         We reserve the right to use Active and Passive Information in order to prevent, detect and investigate
         fraud, security breaches, or any other potentially prohibited or illegal activity.
         We may use any Active Information or Passive Information provided to contact you about various
         changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer. If at any time you do not wish to receive
         such information, you may “opt-out” of doing so by adjusting your email settings in the back office of the
         website.
         Your Information Relating to Hyperlinks
         You might be able to access other websites through our site via hyperlinks. When you do so, you are
         subjecting yourself to their privacy policies and data collection. Please read the privacy policies of those
         sites to ensure you agree with the terms before using such sites.
         Receiving and Sharing of Information from and with Third Parties
         We reserve the right to receive information about you from other third party sources, that help us update,
         expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.
         Furthermore, we may share Personal Information necessary to the prevention of fraud, illegal activities,
         and security breaches. Because of this, it’s possible some of your
         personal information may be shared with fraud prevention agencies. If false or inaccurate information is
         provided and fraud is identified, details of this fraud may be passed on to these agencies. Likewise, law
         enforcement and governmental agencies may access and use certain information pursuant to any law,
         regulation, or subpoena. This applies to information as it relates to both open and closed accounts.
1700 S. Miliken Ave. | Ontario, CA. 91761 | www.vidadivina.com | p: +1(909) 333 5443 | e: compliance@vidadivina.com
                                     ©2019 Vida Divina® Worldwide. All Rights Reserved | Rev: 01-01-19

         Additionally, third parties who perform services for us as it relates to security, payment, etc. (such as
         Internet Service Providers, credit card processors, and merchant banks) may also have access to your
         information in the performance of such necessary services.
         Finally, we may disclose anonymous information about user habits to third party advertisers on our site.
         Should we buy or sell assets of our company, another company may need to review our company’s
         assets, which might include your information, to make business decisions as to whether to acquire such
         assets.
         HOW WE SECURE ACTIVE AND PASSIVE INFORMATION
         We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent
         unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss of Active and Passive Information. Individual
         postings on this site and other communications to our office via email or standard mail may not be secure
         unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your submission of information.
         Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of
         doing so and we respectfully request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these
         means.
         Accessing and Correcting Your Information
         We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our
         Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise
         correct Personally Identifiable Information provided to us, you may edit your information online.
         Protecting Your Information
         We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable
         Information provided from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and
         managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.
         It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site and to promptly advise us if
         you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your
         password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your identification number and password
         are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with
         your identification number and password.
1700 S. Miliken Ave. | Ontario, CA. 91761 | www.vidadivina.com | p: +1(909) 333 5443 | e: compliance@vidadivina.com
                                      ©2019 Vida Divina® Worldwide. All Rights Reserved | Rev: 01-01-19

         Links to Other Websites
         Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience or to provide
         additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If
         you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information
         practices of those websites nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you
         carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
         Children’s Privacy Protection
         We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active
         participant in their child’s online activities. Our site does not target and is not intended for children under
         the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we
         discover personal data from a child through our site, we will eliminate that data. You may learn more
         about protecting children’s privacy online by visiting: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/
         tec08.shtm
         CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
         Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy will be posted on our Site and the date of the
         newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally
         Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you
         acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.
         YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS THAT YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS
         POLICY. YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.
1700 S. Miliken Ave. | Ontario, CA. 91761 | www.vidadivina.com | p: +1(909) 333 5443 | e: compliance@vidadivina.com
                                      ©2019 Vida Divina® Worldwide. All Rights Reserved | Rev: 01-01-19
